{ "sections": [{
     "type": "instructional",
     "body": "Welcome to Learning Hiragana Japanese Characters.\n\nBasic Vowels.  Japanese has 5 basic vowels:\nあ - a - pronounced \"ah\", like the vowel in \"car\"\nい - i - pronounced \"ee\", like \"bee\" or \"key\"\n う - u - pronounced \"u\", like in \"moo\" or \"tube\"\nえ - e - pronounced \"eh\", like in \"end\" or \"bet\"\nお - o - pronounced \"oh\", like in \"joe\" or \"go\"\n\n\nあい (ai) is the Japanese word for \"love\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-a",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nあ",
     "correct-answer": "a",
     "distractors": ["i","u","e","o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-i",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nい",
     "correct-answer": "i",
     "distractors": ["a","u","e","o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-u",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nう",
     "correct-answer": "u",
     "distractors": ["a","i","e","o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-e",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nえ",
     "correct-answer": "e",
     "distractors": ["a","u","i","o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-o",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nお",
     "correct-answer": "o",
     "distractors": ["a","u","e","i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 50
    },
    {
     "type": "instructional",
     "body": "Consonant sounds are combined with the basic vowels to make more characters.\n\n\"K\" characters:\nか - ka - pronounced \"kah\"\nき - ki - pronounced \"key\"\nく - ku - pronounced \"coo\"\nけ - ke - as in \"okay\"\nこ - ko - as in \"coal\"\n\nかく (kaku) is the Japanese word for \"write\""},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ka",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nか",
     "correct-answer": "ka",
     "distractors": ["ki","ku","ke","ko", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ki",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nき",
     "correct-answer": "ki",
     "distractors": ["ka","ku","ke","ko", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ku",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nく",
     "correct-answer": "ku",
     "distractors": ["ki","ka","ke","ko", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ke",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nけ",
     "correct-answer": "ke",
     "distractors": ["ki","ku","ka","ko", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ko",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nこ",
     "correct-answer": "ko",
     "distractors": ["ki","ku","ke","ka", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 100
    },
    {
     "type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"S\" characters:\nさ - sa - pronounced \"saw\"\nし - shi - pronounced \"she\"\nす - su - pronounced \"sue\"\nせ - se - pronounced \"say\"\nそ - so - pronounced \"sew\"\n\nすし (sushi) is a popular Japanese food\n\nBe careful - \"s\" and \"i\" sounds are combined to make \"shi\" NOT \"si\""},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-sa",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nさ",
     "correct-answer": "sa",
     "distractors": ["shi","su","se","so", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-shi",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nし",
     "correct-answer": "shi",
     "distractors": ["sa","su","se","so", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-su",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nす",
     "correct-answer": "su",
     "distractors": ["shi","sa","se","so", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-se",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nせ",
     "correct-answer": "se",
     "distractors": ["shi","su","sa","so", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-so",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nそ",
     "correct-answer": "so",
     "distractors": ["shi","su","se","sa", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 150
    },
    {
     "type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"T\" characters:\nた - ta - like the begining of \"talk\"\nち - chi - like in \"cheetah\"\nつ - tsu - like the begining of \"tsunami\"\nて - te - like in \"take\"\nと - to - pronounced \"toe\"\n\nてつ (tetsu) is the Japanese word for iron.\n\nBe careful - \"t\" and \"i\" sounds are combined to make \"chi\" NOT \"ti\""},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ta",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nた",
     "correct-answer": "ta",
     "distractors": ["chi","tsu","te","to", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-chi",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nち",
     "correct-answer": "chi",
     "distractors": ["ta","tsu","te","to", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-tsu",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nつ",
     "correct-answer": "tsu",
     "distractors": ["chi","ta","te","to", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-te",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nて",
     "correct-answer": "te",
     "distractors": ["chi","tsu","ta","to", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-to",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nと",
     "correct-answer": "to",
     "distractors": ["chi","tsu","te","ta", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 200
    },
    {
     "type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"N\" characters:\nな - na - like the begining of \"not\"\nに - ni - like \"knee\"\nぬ - nu - pronounced \"new\"\nね - ne - like in \"nape\"\nの - no - pronounced \"no\"\n\nなに (nani) is the Japanese word for \"what\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-na",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nな",
     "correct-answer": "na",
     "distractors": ["ni","nu","ne","no", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ni",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nに",
     "correct-answer": "ni",
     "distractors": ["na","nu","ne","no", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-nu",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nぬ",
     "correct-answer": "nu",
     "distractors": ["ni","na","ne","no", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ne",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nね",
     "correct-answer": "ne",
     "distractors": ["ni","nu","na","no", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-no",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nの",
     "correct-answer": "no",
     "distractors": ["ni","nu","ne","na", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 250
    },
    {"type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"N\" characters:\nな - na - like the begining of \"not\"\nに - ni - like \"knee\"\nぬ - nu - pronounced \"new\"\nね - ne - like in \"nape\"\nの - no - pronounced \"no\"\n\nなに (nani) is the Japanese word for \"what\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-na",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nな",
     "correct-answer": "na",
     "distractors": ["ni","nu","ne","no", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ni",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nに",
     "correct-answer": "ni",
     "distractors": ["na","nu","ne","no", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-nu",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nぬ",
     "correct-answer": "nu",
     "distractors": ["ni","na","ne","no", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ne",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nね",
     "correct-answer": "ne",
     "distractors": ["ni","nu","na","no", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-no",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nの",
     "correct-answer": "no",
     "distractors": ["ni","nu","ne","na", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 300
    },
    {"type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"H\" characters:\nは - ha - like in \"hawk\"\nひ - hi - like \"heat\"\nふ - hu - pronounced \"who\"\nへ - he - like in \"head\"\nほ - ho - pronounced \"hoe\"\n\nはい (hai) is the Japanese word for \"yes\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ha",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nは",
     "correct-answer": "ha",
     "distractors": ["hi","hu","he","ho", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-hi",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nひ",
     "correct-answer": "hi",
     "distractors": ["ha","hu","he","ho", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-hu",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nふ",
     "correct-answer": "hu",
     "distractors": ["hi","ha","he","ho", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-he",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nへ",
     "correct-answer": "he",
     "distractors": ["hi","hu","ha","ho", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ho",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nほ",
     "correct-answer": "ho",
     "distractors": ["hi","hu","he","ha", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 350
    },
    {"type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"M\" characters:\nま - ma - like the end of \"grandma\"\nみ - mi - like \"me\"\nむ - mu - pronounced \"moo\"\nめ - me - pronounced \"may\"\nも - mo - pronounced \"mow\"\n\nもも (momo) is the Japanese word for \"peach\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ma",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nま",
     "correct-answer": "ma",
     "distractors": ["mi","mu","me","mo", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-mi",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nみ",
     "correct-answer": "mi",
     "distractors": ["ma","mu","me","mo", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-mu",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nむ",
     "correct-answer": "mu",
     "distractors": ["mi","ma","me","mo", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-me",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nめ",
     "correct-answer": "me",
     "distractors": ["mi","mu","ma","mo", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-mo",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nも",
     "correct-answer": "mo",
     "distractors": ["mi","mu","me","ma", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 400
    },
    {"type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"Y\" characters:\nや - ya - like in \"yawn\"\nゆ - yu - pronounced \"you\"\nよ - yo - like in \"yolk\"\n\nゆき (yuki) is the Japanese word for \"snow\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ya",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nや",
     "correct-answer": "ya",
     "distractors": ["yu","yo", "a", "u", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-yu",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nゆ",
     "correct-answer": "yu",
     "distractors": ["ya","yo", "a","u", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-yo",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nよ",
     "correct-answer": "yo",
     "distractors": ["yu","ya", "o", "u", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 450
    },
    {"type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"R\" characters:\nら - ra - like in \"rock\"\nり - ri - like \"return\"\nる - ru - pronounced \"rue\"\nれ - re - pronounced \"ray\"\nろ - ro - pronounced \"row\"\n\nろく (roku) is the Japanese word for \"six\"."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ra",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nら",
     "correct-answer": "ra",
     "distractors": ["ri","ru","re","ro", "a"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ri",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nり",
     "correct-answer": "ri",
     "distractors": ["ra","ru","re","ro", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ru",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nる",
     "correct-answer": "ru",
     "distractors": ["ri","ra","re","ro", "u"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-re",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nれ",
     "correct-answer": "re",
     "distractors": ["ri","ru","ra","ro", "e"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-ro",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nろ",
     "correct-answer": "ro",
     "distractors": ["ri","ru","re","ra", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 500
    },
    {"type": "instructional",
     "body": "\"W\" characters:\nわ - wa - like in \"walk\"\nを - wo - pronounced \"oh\"\n\nNote that the 'w' on を(wo) is not pronounced."},
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-wa",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nわ",
     "correct-answer": "wa",
     "distractors": ["i","u","e","wo", "o"]
    },
    {
     "type":"add-question",
     "id":"hiragana-wo",
     "prompt":"Match the Japanese character with the sound it makes:\n\nを",
     "correct-answer": "wo",
     "distractors": ["wa","u","e","o", "i"]
    },
    {
     "type":"review",
     "threshold": 5000
    }]
}
